Privacy Policy
==============

Last updated on: December 18, 2024

Privacy Summary

OUR CONTACT INFORMATION  
Future Today Inc.  
Address: Future Today Inc. 3705 Haven Ave, Suite 133 Menlo Park, CA 94025  
Phone number: [+1 888 575 7564](callto:1 888 575 7564)  
Email address: [privacy@futuretodayinc.com](mailto:privacy@futuretodayinc.com)  

* * *

GENERAL INFORMATION

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Do we collect Personal Data? | YES. Some categories include IP addresses, device and advertising identifiers, first name and last name, usage data and other information obtained with cookies and similar tracking technologies.  <br>Click [here](#personal) to read which categories of Personal Data we collect and how we obtain them. |
| Do we process special categories of data, also known as sensitive data or sensitive personal information, such as health data? | NO  |
| Do we sell or share Personal Data? | We support our free Service with ads connected to your location and the content you are viewing. This may be considered as a “sale,” “share,” “profiling”, or “targeted advertising” under certain data protection and privacy laws. Click [here](#do_not_sell) to learn how to opt out. |

PRIVACY RIGHTS

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Can you request not to receive direct marketing from Future Today? | YES. You can just reply to our marketing communication saying you do not want us to send you or your company more marketing communications or click on the unsubscribe link in the communication. Alternatively, you can always contact us by any of [these](#contact_us) methods. |
| Can you request to receive a copy of the Personal Data we have collected about you? | YES, if we can identify you. Please remember that we cannot positively identify the vast majority of our users. While the identifiers we process may be considered Personal Data under applicable data protection laws, in most cases they identify a device rather than a person.  <br>Click [here](#right_to_know) to learn how. |
| Can you withdraw your consent to our processing of your Personal Data? | YES. Click [here](#withdraw) to learn how. |
| Can you request to have your data deleted? | YES. Click [here](#delete) to learn how. |
| Can you request not to have your data sold (shared with advertising partners)? | YES. Click [here](#do_not_sell) to learn how to opt out of ad tracking. |
| Will we discriminate against you for exercising your privacy rights? | **NO**. Click [here](#non) to learn more about your right not to be discriminated against. |

SECURITY

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Do we protect your Personal Data? | YES. Click [here](#security) to learn more about how we protect your Personal Data. |

* * *

Introduction

Future Today Inc. (“Future Today”, “we”, “us”, “our”) takes the protection of personal data (“Personal Data”) very seriously. Future Today operates websites, mobile applications, OTT applications, and Connected TV applications (collectively, the “Service”). Please read this privacy policy (the “Policy”) to learn what we are doing with your Personal Data, how we protect it, and what privacy rights you may have under applicable data protection and privacy laws, such as the European Union General Data Protection Regulation, the United Kingdom General Data Protection Regulation (together, “GDPR”), the Canada Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA), the California Consumer Privacy Act, the Colorado Privacy Act, the Connecticut Act Concerning Personal Data Privacy and Online Monitoring, the Oregon Consumer Privacy Act, the Texas Data Privacy and Security Act, the Utah Consumer Privacy Act, the Virginia Consumer Data Protection Act, and similar state laws as they take effect (collectively, the “U.S. Privacy Laws”).

* * *

Scope of this Privacy Policy

What Is Covered by this Privacy Policy?  
This Policy addresses Personal Data that we:  

* Receive directly through our Service.
* Receive from individuals that contact us.
* Receive from our business partners, including content partners.
* Process to promote our products and services.

What Is Not Covered by this Privacy Notice?  
Human Resources Personal Data  
This Notice does not apply to the Personal Data of employees, job applicants, contractors, business owners, directors, officers, and medical staff of Future Today.  
Information Which Does Not Constitute Personal Data  
If we do not maintain information in a manner that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could be reasonably linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular individual or household, such information is not considered Personal Data, and, consequently, this Policy will not apply to our processing of that information. When data is deidentified (as defined under applicable U.S. Privacy Laws), we maintain it in deidentified form and do not attempt to re-identify the information.

What Can You Find in this Policy?

This Policy tells you, among other things:  

* [Your rights with regard to the Personal Data we collect about you](#rights) and [how can you exercise those rights](#privacy_rights)

* * *

Our Role with Respect to Your Personal Data

Within the scope of this Policy, Future Today acts as a data controller or “business” for the Personal Data we process. This means that we decide how and why Personal Data is collected and further processed.

* * *

Lawful Bases for Processing

The GDPR and other applicable data protection laws require that we have a valid reason to use your Personal Data. This is called the “lawful basis for processing.” We may process your Personal Data:

* Because you gave your consent.
* Because we need to perform a contract with you.
* Because we have a legitimate interest in processing your Personal Data and it is not overridden by your rights. Some of those interests include:
    * Monetizing your use of the Service with ads which are relevant to you.
    * Enhancing, modifying, personalizing or otherwise improving our Service and communications for the benefits of our customers.
    * Identifying and preventing fraud.
    * Enhancing the security of our network and information systems.
    * Determining the success of our Service, promotional campaigns, and advertising.
* Because we need to comply with the law.
* On another ground, as required or permitted by law.

When we rely on legitimate interests as a lawful basis of processing, you have the right to ask us more about how we decided to choose this legal basis and object to this processing. To do so, please use the contact details provided [here](#contact_us).  
Where we process your or your child’s Personal Data based on your consent, you may withdraw it at any time. However, this will not affect the lawfulness of our processing before your withdrawal of consent. It will also not affect the validity of our processing of Personal Data performed on other lawful grounds.  
Where we receive your Personal Data as part of the provision of the Service to/from you or your brand to fulfill a contract, we require such Personal Data to be able to carry out the contract. Without that necessary Personal Data, we will not be able to provide the Service to you or fulfill our contractual obligations with you.

* * *

What Personal Data We Process, How We Obtain It and How We Use It

The sections below describe the categories of Personal Data we have collected about you in the last twelve months, the sources of such Personal Data and the purposes of processing. We do not collect sensitive personal information, as defined under the U.S. Privacy Laws.

Service Users

If you use our Service, we collect and process your Personal Data as described in the table below:

|     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| **Category** | **Type of Personal Data** | **How We Obtain It** | **Purpose of Processing** |
| Identifier | Your first and last name and your email address | You provide it to us directly. For example, you provide it when you fill out a form, contact us to ask a question, post a comment or inquiry via our social media channels, or exercise your privacy rights. | To answer your queries and requests. To fulfill our legal obligations, such as our obligation to process and log your data protection requests under applicable data protection and privacy laws. |
| Identifier | Your phone number |
| Identifier | Your email address\*  <br>\*We do not collect your email address for these purposes currently, but we may start collecting it in the future. | You provide it to us directly | To provide and maintain our Service.<br><br>To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so.<br><br>To provide recommendations based the content you have been viewing on our Service.<br><br>To present relevant advertising to you based on your general location and the content type you have been viewing on our Service.<br><br>For example, if you watch cooking content in the USA on our Service, you will see advertising for cooking-related content in English in other parts of our Service. |
| Your IP address, unique advertising identifiers and device identifiers (such as your mobile device unique ID) | We collect it automatically. Specifically, your browser or app sends it to us thanks to cookies and similar tracking technologies. |
| Internet or other similar network activity (usage data_)_ | Your browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit to our Service, the time spent on our Service, the content that you watch in our Service, your interactions with advertisements, the advertisements that were shown to you, and certain diagnostic data |     | To undertake internal research for technological development of the Service.<br><br>To verify, maintain or enhance the quality and safety of the Service.<br><br>To provide better content recommendations so you can enjoy an enhanced user’s experience.<br><br>To remember content you have bookmarked so you can easily find it later. |
| Geolocation data | Your general location (such as city or zip code) | Your IP address may reveal it to us. | To present content available in your country and language. |
| Inferences drawn from other Personal Data | Your preferences in relation to the part of our Service you have used | We infer it from your activity on our Service, such as title selections and content you have watched and bookmarked. | To provide better content recommendations so you can enjoy an enhanced user’s experience. |

Content Partners

If you or your organization submit content to be streamed in our Service we process information as described in the table below. Please note that, depending on the context of you and your organization’s relationship with us, and the applicable U.S. Privacy Laws, not all of this information may be considered Personal Data.

|     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| **Category** | **Type of Personal Data** | **How We Obtain It** | **Purpose of Processing** |
| Identifier | Your first and last name and your (professional) email address | You or your organization provide it to us. For example, you provide this Personal Data when you contact us or when your personal details are included in a contract with us. | To contact you regarding the content that you or your organization submit to us or our business relationship with you. |
| Professional related information: | The organization you collaborate with |
| Audiovisual information | Your image and voice as recorded in the content provided by you or your organization<br><br>Any other personal information you voluntarily provide within the content | To contact you regarding the content that you or your brand submit to us or our business relationship with you. |

Business Contacts

Future Today may collect information regarding business contacts (employees, owners, directors, officers, contractors, sole proprietors) in the course of communicating with other entities and governmental agencies or making transactions between Future Today and other entities. The table below describes how we process the information of our business contacts. Please note that depending on the context of the business contacts’ relationship with us, and the applicable U.S. Privacy Laws, not all of this information may be considered Personal Data.

|     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| **Category** | **Type of Personal Data** | **How We Obtain It** | **Purpose of Processing** |
| Identifier | Your first and last name and your (professional) email address | You or your entity provide it to us. For example, you provide us with your Personal Data when you or your entity contact Future Today or include your personal details in a contract with Future Today | To contact you about Future Today’s business relationship with you or the company you represent and fulfill our legal obligations and enforce our rights.<br><br>To send you marketing communications about our business that we think may interest the entity you represent. |
| Identifier | Your (professional) phone number |
| Professional related information | Your job title and the company you work for |

* * *

Tracking Technologies

We may use tracking technologies in our Service, such as cookies, beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service. Some of our apps may use tracking technologies to provide targeted advertising, website functionality, authentication (session management), usage analytics (web analytics), to remember your settings, and to generally improve our Service.  
For more information about our use of cookies and tracking technologies, please see the ["Cookie Information"](#cookie_information) section below.

* * *

Do Not Track Signals from Web Browsers

Our Service does not have the capability to respond to “Do Not Track” signals received from web browsers.

* * *

Limit Ad Tracking with Your Smart TV

Many smart TVs offer users the capability to define their tracking settings to limit ad tracking. Future Today will stop sharing your information with third parties for advertising purposes in real time if it receives a signal that you have changed your settings to limit ad tracking.  
Read below to learn how to turn off your Smart TV tracking features.

* **AppleTV**:
    * Go to **Settings > General > Privacy**, and turn the “Limit Ad Tracking” option on.
    * If you have an older AppleTV, go to **Settings > General**and change “Send Data to Apple” to “**No**.”
* **Roku**:
    * Go to **Settings > Privacy > Advertising**, then check “Limit ad tracking.” Note: This setting is also available on Roku streaming gadgets.
* **Samsung**: Go to Settings > Support, scroll down to Terms & Policies, and turn off “Internet-based Advertising.”
* **Samba TV**: Go to **Interactive TV Settings > Privacy**, then enabling “Limit Ad Tracking.”
* **Vizio**:
    * On older Vizio TV sets that use Vizio Internet Apps (VIA), go to the TV’s System, and then: **Reset & Admin > Smart Interactivity > “Off**.”
    * On Vizio smart TVs that use the newer SmartCast system, go to **System > Reset & Admin** and toggle the setting labelled “Viewing Data” to “Off.”
* **LG**: Go to Settings > All Settings > scroll down to General > About This TV > User Agreements > toggle Personalized Advertising to “Off.”
* **Amazon Fire**: Go to **Settings > Preferences** then scroll and click on “Right to Privacy Settings.” Turn off the settings labeled “Collect App and Over-the-Air Usage Data” and “Interest-based Ads.”

If your device does not offer these kinds of features, please contact us by following [these instructions](#privacy_rights).

* * *

Cookie Information

Our websites, futuretodayinc.com, fawesome.tv, use cookies for various purposes, some of which are necessary for essential functionality of the website, while others are not essential but help us improve the service or serve ads. A cookie is a small text file stored on your device (computer, phone, tablet, etc.) that contains information about your browser and online activity. This information often consists of a string of numbers and letters that uniquely identifies your device.  
You can configure your cookie choices by interacting with the banners on the websites. When you accept all cookies, you consent to the processing of the information collected by the cookie for the purpose of each cookie noted below, which could include processing of sensitive data, selling or sharing information, targeted advertising and profiling.  
You can alter the configuration of your browser to reject certain types of cookies. Please note, however, that if you reject certain cookies, you may not be able to access and use all of the features on our Website. For more information about how to manage cookies, please visit [https://www.aboutcookies.org/](https://www.aboutcookies.org/).  
You may also control your online behavioral advertising preferences and opt out from having your data processed by certain marketing companies by visiting [http://www.youronlinechoices.com/](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/) and [http://optout.aboutads.info/](http://optout.aboutads.info/). Please note that, however, managing these preferences will not turn off internet advertisements in general. You will still receive the same number of advertisements, but those advertisements will be less reflective of your interests, as indicated by your web browsing habits. In addition, please note that the opt-out preferences that you set using these tools may be nullified if you delete your cookies after setting them.  
Read on to learn about the specific cookies we use on our websites.

Essential Cookies

The following cookies are necessary for our websites to function properly, and we cannot turn them off in our systems. You may still be able to set your browser to block or alert you about some of these cookies, but if you do block these cookies, some parts of our websites will not work.

|     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| **Name of cookie** | **First or third party** | **Duration** | **Purpose** |
| ft\_\_token | First party | One day | This cookie sets an encrypted token to fetch an API response. This cookie is required for security purposes. |
| ft\_corp\_web\_user\_consent | First party | One week | This cookie allows the website to save and respect your cookie consent choices. |
| PHPSESSID | First party(wp.staging.ifood.tv) | 1 year | This cookie ensures that the server can remember who the user is between different page loads or actions on the website, facilitating a consistent and personalized experience. |
| ft\_gdprUserConsent | First party | 1 year | This cookie allows the website to save and respect your cookie consent choices. |

Analytics Cookies

The following cookies allow us, among other things, to count website visits and traffic sources so that we can measure and improve the performance of our website. They help us to know which pages are the most – and least – popular, and see how visitors move around the website. If you do not allow these cookies we will not know when you have visited our Website, and we will not be able to monitor our website’s performance.

|     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| **Name of cookie** | **First or third party** | **Duration** | **Purpose** |
| \_ga\_xxxxxxxxx, \_ga | First party | 1 year | These are Google Analytics cookies and they are included in each page request in a site and used to calculate visitor, session and campaign data for the site's analytics reports. More information about Google's use of cookies can be found at [https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies?hl=en-US](https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies?hl=en-US). |

Functional Cookies

The following cookies enable the websites to provide enhanced functionality and personalization. They may be used by us or by third-party providers whose services we have added to our pages. If you do not allow these cookies, then some or all of these services may not function properly.

|     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| **Name of cookie** | **First or third party** | **Duration** | **Purpose** |
| ft\_device\_id | First party | One year | This cookie is used for analytics and to power personalization features such as “recently watched.” |
| ft\_appInstallDL | First party | One day | This cookie is set to remember that you already clicked on the “Download” App” button and refrain from showing you the same popup for 24 hours. |
| VISITOR\_INFO1\_LIVE | Third party (Google / YouTube) | 5 months | This cookie is used by YouTube to track user preferences and remember video player settings. You can learn more about Google's cookies here: [https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies?hl=en). |
| VISITOR\_PRIVACY\_METADATA | Third party (Google / YouTube) | 5 months | This cookie is associated with YouTube, the Google service, and it is used to track and enrich the user’s privacy settings on the Youtube platform. You can learn more about Google's cookies here: [https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies?hl=en). |
| YSC | Third party (Google / YouTube) | 1 year | This cookie is associated with YouTube and it ensures that requests within a browsing session are made by the user, and not by other sites. This cookie lasts for the duration of a user’s browsing session. You can learn more about Google's cookies here: [https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies?hl=en). |
| SEARCH\_SAMESITE | Third party (Google / YouTube) | 1 year | This cookie is associated with Google is used to prevent the browser from sending this cookie along with cross-site requests. You can learn more about Google's cookies here: [https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies?hl=en). |
| AEC | Third party (Google / YouTube) | 6 months | This cookie is associated with Google and ensures that requests within a browsing session are made by the user, and not by other sites. This cookie prevents malicious sites from acting on behalf of a user without that user’s knowledge. This cookie lasts for 6 months. You can learn more about Google's cookies here: [https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies?hl=en). |
| \_\_Secure-1PAPISIDS  <br>ID  <br>SID  <br>SSID  <br>SAPISID  <br>\_\_Secure-1PSID  <br>\_\_Secure-1PSIDCC  <br>\_\_Secure-1PSIDTS  <br>\_\_Secure-3PAPISID  <br>\_\_Secure-3PSID  <br>\_\_Secure-3PISDCC  <br>\_\_Secure-3PSIDTS  <br>CC  <br>APISID  <br>HSID  <br>APISID  <br>DV  <br>NID  <br>SAPISID | Third party (Google / YouTube) | 12-13 months | This cookie contains digitally signed and encrypted records of a user’s Google Account ID and most recent sign-in time. This cookie, together with the information from another cookie, allows Google to block many types of attack, such as attempts to steal the content of forms submitted in Google services. You can learn more about Google's cookies here: [https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies?hl=en). |

Advertising Cookies

The following cookies may be used on our websites by our advertising partners (or set directly by our advertising partners) to collect data about your online activity. They record your visits to our website, the pages you have visited, and the links you have followed. They are used by our advertising partners to build a profile of your interests and show you relevant advertisements on our website as well as other sites. For example, they’re used to detect when you click on an ad and show you ads based on your social media interests and browsing history.  
If you do not allow these cookies, you will experience fewer targeted advertisements.

|     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| **Name of cookie** | **First or third party** | **Duration** | **Purpose** |
| \_gcl\_au | First party | Persistent | This cookie is used by Google AdSense to experiment with advertisement efficiency across websites using their services. It helps track the conversion rates and improve the performance of ads by understanding user interactions. This ensures that ads displayed to users are relevant and effective. |
| \_gclxxxx | First party | 2 months | This cookie stores campaign information in order to provide Google Ads with a more reliable way to measure the interactions customers have with your business. Google Analytics writes campaign information to cookie when a user opens a page on a site via a URL that employs Google Ads auto-tagging. You can learn more about this cookie here: [https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/7519794?hl=en&sjid=6454804752743697683-EU#zippy=%2Csecciones-de-este-art%C3%ADculo%2Cin-this-article](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/7519794?hl=en&sjid=6454804752743697683-EU#zippy=%2Csecciones-de-este-art%C3%ADculo%2Cin-this-article). |
| IDE | Third party (doubleclick.net – Google) | 1 year | This is an advertising cookie associated with Google's DoubleClick service and is used to track user interactions with ads. |
| test\_cookie | Third party (doubleclick.net – Google) | A few seconds | This cookie is set by DoubleClick (which is owned by Google) to determine if the website visitor's browser supports cookies. You can learn more about Google and cookies here: [https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies?hl=en). |

* * *

How Long Do We Keep Your Personal Data?

We will retain your Personal Data for as long as is necessary to fulfill the purpose for which we collected your Personal Data and any other permitted linked purpose and in compliance with our data retention policies. For example, we will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.  
Generally, we retain usage data for a shorter period, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.  
If your Personal Data is used for more than one purpose, we will retain it until the purpose with the longest retention period expires; but we will stop using it for the purpose with a shorter retention period once that period expires. Our retention periods are also based on our business needs and good practice.

* * *

Our Data Sharing Practices

Future Today engages companies, agents, and contractors (“Service Providers“) who perform services for business purposes on our behalf or assist us with the provision of the Service to you. Some of those Service Providers may need to process your Personal Data to provide their services to us. We do not authorize our Service Providers to use or disclose your Personal Data except in connection with providing services for business purposes to us (which can include maintaining and improving their services).  
We also disclose your Personal Data to third-party advertising networks as described below.

Service Users

These tables describe how we have disclosed your Personal Data to Service Providers and third parties and for what business purposes in the last twelve months.

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Type of Personal Data** | **Categories of Service Providers and Third Parties We Disclose Personal Data to** |
| Your first and last name and your email address | Email service providers<br><br>Hosting providers<br><br>Cloud productivity and collaboration tools providers |
| Your phone number |
| Your IP address, unique advertising identifiers, cookie identifiers and device identifiers (such as your mobile device unique ID) | Analytics services providers<br><br>App development software tools providers<br><br>Advertising networks (such as digital advertising marketplaces, supply-side platforms, and platforms to manage video and banner advertising), who may subsequently send your Personal Data to demand side platforms, ad exchanges, agencies, agency trading desks and ad networks<br><br>Hosting providers |
| Your browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit to our Service, the time spent on our Service, the content that you watch in our Service, your interactions with advertisements, the advertisements that were shown to you, and certain diagnostic data |
| Your general location |
| Your preferences in relation to the part of our Service you have used |

When you use the Service, we make your advertising identifier, device identifier and cookie identifiers available to advertising networks. This may be considered a “sale” or “sharing” of personal information or Personal Data under certain U.S. Privacy Laws. See “Your Privacy Rights” below to learn how to opt out of this “sale” or “sharing”.

Content Partners

These tables describe how we have disclosed your Personal Data to Service Providers and for what business purposes in the last twelve months. Please note that depending on the context of you and your organization’s relationship with us, and the applicable U.S. Privacy Laws, not all of this information may be considered Personal Data.

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Type of Personal Data** | **Categories of Service Providers We Disclose Personal Data to** |
| Your first and last name and your (professional) email address | Email service providers<br><br>Ticketing system software providers<br><br>Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software providers<br><br>Hosting providers<br><br>Productivity and collaboration tool service providers |
| The organization you collaborate with |
| Your image and voice as recorded in the content provided by you or your organization | Hosting providers<br><br>Content delivery network (CDN) services providers |

We do not sell Content Partners’ Personal Data to third parties.

Business Contacts

These tables describe how we have disclosed your Personal Data to Service Providers and for what business purposes in the last twelve months. Please note that depending on the context of the business contacts’ relationship with us, and the applicable US Privacy Laws, not all of this information may be considered Personal Data.

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Type of Personal Data** | **Purpose of Processing** |
| Your first and last name and your (professional) email address | Email service providers<br><br>Ticketing system software providers<br><br>CRM software providers<br><br>Hosting providers<br><br>Productivity and collaboration tool service providers |
| Your (professional) phone number |
| Your job title and the company you work for |

We do not “sell” or “share” Business Contacts’ Personal Data to/with third parties.

Other Disclosures of Personal Data

If Future Today is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Data may be transferred. In that case, we will provide notice before your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Policy.  
Under certain circumstances, Future Today may also be required by law to disclose your Personal Data in response to valid requests by public authorities (for example a court or a government agency).  
We may also disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

* Comply with a legal obligation, official investigations or legal proceedings (whether initiated by governmental/law enforcement officials, or private parties) .
* Protect and defend the rights or property of Future Today.
* Prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service.
* Protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public.
* Protect against legal liability.

We reserve the right to use, transfer, sell, and share aggregated, anonymous, or deidentified data for any legal purpose. Such data does not include any Personal Data. The purposes may include analyzing usage trends or seeking compatible advertisers, sponsors, and customers.

Transfers of Personal Data

Your Personal Data may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers and servers located outside of your state, province, country, or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection and privacy laws may be different than the laws in your jurisdiction.  
Future Today is established in the United States of America (USA). If you choose to provide information to Future Today, including by using the Service, your Personal Data will be processed, stored, and maintained inside and outside the USA. If you do not want your data to be processed in the USA or other countries, do not use the Service, and do not provide us with your Personal Data.  
Future Today will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Policy. No transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including safeguards protecting the security of your data and other personal information.

Transfers of Personal Data Outside the European Economic Area or the United Kingdom

Some of the third parties we send Personal Data to are located outside of the European Economic Area (“**EEA**”) and the United Kingdom (“**UK**”). In some cases, the European Commission or the UK Secretary of State may have determined that the data protection laws of some countries provide a level of protection equivalent to EU or UK law. You can see [here](https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/international-dimension-data-protection/adequacy-decisions_en) the list of countries that the European Commission has recognized as providing an adequate level of protection to personal data.  
We will only transfer your Personal Data to third parties outside the EEA or the UK to countries not recognized as providing an adequate level of protection to Personal Data when there are appropriate safeguards in place. We may achieve such enhanced protection by placing obligations on the recipient of the data with the [Standard Contractual Clauses](https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/international-dimension-data-protection/standard-contractual-clauses-scc_en) approved by the European Commission under [Article 46.2 of the GDPR](https://gdpr.verasafe.com/article-46/).

* * *

What Privacy Rights Do You Have?

You have specific rights regarding your Personal Data that we collect and process.  
In this section, we first describe those rights and then we explain [how you can exercise those rights](#top). Please note that since we do not collect sensitive Personal Data, we do not offer a “right to limit” the processing of sensitive personal information under U.S. Privacy Laws. Similarly, we do not profile you to make decisions with legal or similarly significant effects and therefore do not offer a right to opt out of such processing.

* * *

Right to Know What Happens to Your Personal Data

This is also called the right to be informed. It means that you have the right to obtain from us all information regarding our data processing activities that concern you (or your child), such as how we collect and use your Personal Data, how long we will keep it, and who it will be shared with, among other things. This Privacy Policy provides you with the information required by that right, and if we update our processing activities we will notify you as set forth in the “Changes to this Policy” section below.

* * *

Right to Know What Personal Data We Have About You

This is also called the right of access. This right allows you to ask for full details of the Personal Data we hold on you, including confirmation of whether we process Personal Data concerning you (or your child), and, where that is the case, a copy or access to the Personal Data and certain related information.  
Once we receive and [confirm](#privacy_rights) that the request came from you or your authorized agent, we will disclose to you:

* The categories of your Personal Data that we process
* The categories of sources for your Personal Data
* Our purposes for processing your Personal Data
* Where possible, the retention period for your Personal Data, or, if not possible, the criteria used to determine the retention period
* The categories of third parties with whom we share your Personal Data
* If we carry out automated decision-making, including profiling, meaningful information about the logic involved, as well as the significance and the envisaged consequences of such processing for you
* The specific pieces of Personal Data we process about you in an easily sharable format
* If we sold or disclosed your Personal Data for a business purpose, the categories of Personal Data and categories of recipients of that Personal Data for both sale and disclosure
* If we rely on legitimate interests as a lawful basis to process your Personal Data, the specific legitimate interests
* The appropriate safeguards used to transfer Personal Data from the EEA or the UK to a third country, if applicable

Under some circumstances, we may deny your access request. In that event, we will respond to you with the reason for the denial.

* * *

Right to Change Your Personal Data

This is also called the right to rectification or correction. This right entitles you to ask us to correct without undue delay anything that you think is wrong with the Personal Data we have on file about you (or your child), and to complete any incomplete Personal Data.

* * *

Right to Delete Your Personal Data

This is called the **right to erasure, right to deletion, or the right to be forgotten**. This right means you can ask for your Personal Data to be deleted.  
Sometimes we can delete your information, but other times it is not possible for either technical or legal reasons. If that is the case, [we will consider if we can limit how we use it](#right_to_ask). We will also inform you of our reason for denying your deletion request.

* * *

Right to Ask us to Limit How We Process Your Personal Data

This is called the right to restrict processing. It is the right to ask us to only use or store your Personal Data for certain purposes. You have this right in certain instances, such as where you believe the data is inaccurate or the processing activity is unlawful.

* * *

Right to Ask Us to Stop Using Your Personal Data

This is called the **right to object**. This is your right to tell us to indefinitely stop using your Personal Data. You have this right where we rely on a legitimate interest of ours (or of a third party) as the lawful basis for processing your Personal Data. You may also object at any time to the processing of your Personal Data for _direct_ marketing purposes.  
We will stop processing the relevant Personal Data unless:

* we have compelling legitimate grounds for the processing that override your interests, rights, or freedoms; or

* we need to continue processing your Personal Data to establish, exercise, or defend a legal claim.

* * *

Right to Port or Move Your Personal Data

This is called the **right to data portability**. It is the right to ask for and receive a portable copy of your Personal Data that you have given us or that we have observed from your use of our services, so that you can:  

* Move it;
* Copy it;
* Keep it for yourself.; and/or
* Transfer it to another organization.

Note that under the GDPR, the right to data portability only applies when:

* our lawful basis for processing this information is consent or for the performance of a contract; and
* we are carrying out the processing by automated means.

Please note that, under the GDPR, the right does not cover any data that we may have created based on the data you have provided to us.  
When this right applies to you and it is technically feasible, we will provide your Personal Data in a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format. When you request this information electronically, we will provide you with a copy in electronic format.

* * *

Right to Withdraw Your Consent

Where we rely on your consent to process your Personal Data, you may withdraw your consent at any time. If you withdraw your consent, our use of your Personal Data before you withdraw is still lawful.  
If you have given consent for your details to be shared with a third party and wish to withdraw this consent, please also contact the relevant third party to change your preferences.

* * *

Right to Non-Discrimination

We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your privacy rights. Unless the applicable data protection or privacy laws permit it, we will not:

* deny you the Service.
* charge you different prices or rates for the Service including through granting discounts or other benefits or imposing penalties.
* provide you a different level or quality of the Service.
* suggest that you may receive a different price or rate for the Service or a different level or quality of the Service.

* * *

Your Right to Opt Out of the Sale, , Sharing of Personal Data or Targeted Advertising

Our disclosure of certain device-based information such as your device and advertising identifiers may qualify as a “sale,” “sharing,” “profiling”, or “targeted advertising” under certain data protection and privacy laws.  
Some of those laws give you the right to opt out of such “sales,” “sharing,” “profiling”, or targeted advertising. To exercise this right to opt-out, see “How Can You Exercise Your Privacy Rights?” below.  
In addition, you may alter your settings in your device as explained in [this](#limit_ad) section. If your device does not offer options to limit ad tracking, contact us as we explain [here](#privacy_rights).  
Please consider that when you change your device tracking preferences to limit ad tracking or we handle the request for you, you will receive the same number of ads, but they will be less relevant to you.  
Once you make an opt-out request, we will not ask you to reauthorize the sale or sharing of your Personal Data for at least twelve months. However, if you change your mind, you may opt back into Personal Data sales, sharing or targeted advertising at any time by changing your preferences in the Future Today Privacy Center within the Service.  
Depending on where you live, you may have the right to opt out through a Global Privacy Control (“GPC”) enabled browser setting. If you have this right, when you use your Service with a GPC-enabled browser, we will treat our initial receipt of the GPC signal as a valid request to opt out, as defined by applicable U.S. Privacy Laws granting this right. Please note that if you are logged out, our processing of the signal will be limited to the specific browser that you are using. You may need to renew your opt‑out choice if you use a different browser to access our Service.  
We do not knowingly “sell” or “share” the Personal Data of individuals that we know are less than sixteen (16) years old.

* * *

Your Right to Opt into the Sale of Personal Data

If you have directed us not to sell your Personal Data, you can opt into the sale of your Personal Data at any time by changing your ad-tracking preferences in your smart device as we explain [here](#limit_ad). If your device does not offer options to enable again ad tracking, contact us as we explain [here](#privacy_rights).  
In addition, we do not knowingly sell the Personal Data of individuals that we know are less than sixteen (16) years old.

* * *

How Can You Exercise Your Privacy Rights?

To exercise any of the rights described above, to get assistance to exercise those rights, please use the contact details available in the [**Contact Us**](#contact_us) section and provide us with your **email address** (so we can contact you about your request) and **your device ID** ([Don’t know how to find it?](http://futuretodayinc.com/ccpa.html)) if your requests relates to the Personal Data we may process in the context of our Service.  
**Please email us at [privacy@futuretodayinc.com](mailto:privacy@futuretodayinc.com)**

* * *

Verification of Your Identity

To correctly respond to your privacy rights requests (except opt-out requests), we need to confirm that YOU made the request. Consequently, we may require additional information to confirm that you are who you say you are.

* * *

Verification of Authority

If you are submitting a request on behalf of somebody else, we will need to verify your authority to act on behalf of that individual. When contacting us, please provide us with proof that the individual gave you signed permission to submit this request, a valid power of attorney on behalf of the individual, or proof of parental responsibility or legal guardianship. Alternatively, you may ask the individual to directly contact us by using the contact details above to verify their identity with Future Today and confirm with us that they gave you permission to submit this request.

* * *

Response Timing and Format of Our Responses

We will confirm the receipt of your request within ten (10) business days, and, in that communication, we will also describe our identity verification process (if needed) and when you should expect a response, unless we have already granted or denied the request.  
Please allow us up to thirty (30) calendar days to reply to your requests (except requests to stop selling your Personal Data) from the day we received your request. If we need more time (up to ninety (90) days in total), we will inform you of the reason why and the extension period in writing.  
If your request is covered by the CCPA, consider that we will only cover the twelve-month period preceding the moment we receive your request in any disclosures we provide you with.  
We will act upon your request to opt out from the sale of your Personal Data within fifteen (15) business days. We will also notify the third parties to whom we sold your Personal Data of your request and instruct them not to further sell your Personal Data. We will inform you about this in ninety (90) calendar days from the receipt of your request.  
If we cannot satisfy a request, we will explain why in our response. For data portability requests, we will choose a format to provide your Personal Data that is readily usable and should allow you to transmit the information from one entity to another entity without difficulty.  
We will not charge a fee for processing or responding to your requests. However, we may charge a fee if we determine that your request is excessive, repetitive, or manifestly unfounded. In those cases, we will tell you why we made that determination and provide you with a cost estimate before completing your request.

* * *

Right to Lodge a Complaint with a Supervisory Authority

If the GDPR applies to our processing of your Personal Data, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority if you are not satisfied with how we process your Personal Data.  
Specifically, you can lodge a complaint in the Member State of your habitual residence, place of work, or the alleged violation of the GDPR.

* * *

Privacy of Children

Protecting the privacy of children is especially important to us. When we provide our free Service, we do not attempt to associate information with particular individuals. Any accounts with our service must be for ages 16+, and viewers under the age of sixteen (16) must use the Service under adult supervision. As a result, we do not knowingly collect information about anyone under the age of sixteen  
We do recognize that certain parts of our Service may be child-directed in terms of the content. For those parts of our Service, Future Today adheres to the U.S. Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (“COPPA”) and the guidelines of the Children’s Advertising Review Unit (“CARU”) of the Council of Better Business Bureaus, Inc. To the extent parts of our Service are child-directed, we strictly limit the data collection to device information necessary to provide the Service, we mask IP addresses and IP addresses, we do not process the information for targeted advertising, and we do not collect any direct personal identifiers or make any attempts to identify individuals under the age of thirteen (13). Please note that we may still serve geo-targeted contextual advertising (such as an advertisement for a child’s toy or parenting product) and process the information for frequency capping purposes and other operational advertising purposes, but that advertising will not be based on the individual viewer.  
As the parent or guardian, please help us protect your children’s privacy by instructing them never to provide personal information (like their full name, e-mail address, home address, telephone number, etc.) without your permission. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with information that would allow us or anybody to directly identify them (“personally identifiable information”), please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected personally identifiable information from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers. Parents can also contact us to exercise their rights to access, modify, delete, or stop further collection of their child’s personal information.

* * *

Data Integrity & Security

We are strongly committed to keeping your Personal Data safe. We have implemented and will maintain technical, administrative, and physical measures that are reasonably designed to help protect your Personal Data from unauthorized processing. Unauthorized processing includes unauthorized access, exfiltration, theft, disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

* * *

Changes to this Policy

If we make any changes to this Policy, we will post the revised Policy to this web page. We will also update the “Last updated” date. By continuing to use our Service after we post any of these changes, you accept the modified Policy. We may communicate any changes with you from time to time in a manner we determine.

* * *

Contact Us

If you have any questions about this or our processing of your Personal Data, or want to submit a privacy rights request, please write an email at [privacy@futuretodayinc.com](mailto:privacy@futuretodayinc.com) or call at [+1 888 575 7564](callto:1 888 575 7564) or by postal mail at:

Future Today Inc.  
3723 Haven Ave Ste 133, Menlo Park, CA 94025

If you are submitting a privacy rights request, include the information we mention in [this](#privacy_rights) Section of the Policy to enable us to locate you in our systems.

* * *

Future Today Inc.  
3705 Haven Ave,  
Suite 133 Menlo Park,  
CA 94025

Follow Us On [](https://www.linkedin.com/company/future-today-inc/)

© 2021, Future Today, Inc.

All right reserved.
